A Guide to the Oral History Collection, 1976-1981
Archives and Special Collections Department, L. Douglas Wilder Library, Virginia Union University
Archives and Special Collections Department, L. Douglas Wilder Library, Virginia Union University
Oral History Collection, 1976-1981
Archives and Special Collections Department, L. Douglas Wilder Library, Virginia Union University
MS-004
100 items (0.5 linear feet)
Administrative Information
Conditions Governing Access
The collection is open for research use.
Immediate Source of Acquisition
Collected by and received from Verdelle Bradley.
Physical Access
Audio tapes unavailable for use for preservation purposes.
Scope and Content
Oral history interviews conducted in the late 1970's as part of an oral history project at Virginia Union University organized by then Head Librarian, Verdelle Bradley. Also included is a transcript (unit five) for an interview conducted in Ohio by Virginia Union professor Norma M. Goode that was given to Mrs. Bradley for inclusion in this collection
Note that this inventory continues first with a list of oral histories, and then with a more detailed description of each transcript. Units six, seven and eight have not been transcribed. Units are in no particular order. All transcripts have been preservation photocopied.
Index Terms
Persons:
Braxton, William H.; Lewis, Leah V.; McCreary, Edward D.; Mitchell, Thomas; Cheeks, Robert S.; King, Nona; Robinson, E.; Stewart, E. G.; Eggleston, Lemuel V.; Evans, Preston H.; Fox, William H.; Harris, Lureatha J.; Harvey, Perry
Contents List
- Braxton, William H. (b. 1898) (Item 1)
  Audiotape available
- Lewis, Leah V. (Item 2)
- McCreary, Edward D. (Item 3)
- Mitchell, Thomas (b. 1916) (Item 4)
- Cheeks, Robert S. (b. 1895) (Item 5)
- King, Nona (Item 6)
  Transcript not available.
- Robinson, E. (b. 1905) (Item 7)
- Stewart, E. G. (Item 8)
- Eggleston, Lemuel V. (b. 1882) (Item 9)
- Evans, Preston H. (Item 10)
- Fox, William H. (b. 1890) (Item 11)
- Harris, Lureatha J. (b. 1911) (Item 12)
- Harvey, Perry (b. 1886) (Item 13)